[Music]
In the name of God, see the fifth issue, it's gone,
number 9, Mr. Zare'i, hello, Mr. Reza, good evening,
hello, good evening, Mr. Zare'i, at my service, Mr.
Reza, I didn't have any specific questions, just a question
about the subject you are teaching. Now, you have
seen my journal. For example, I had the concepts of
DPW. Talk to each other about the things you taught before.
Okay, Zarrian, put your mind
aside.
Well, it's hard. Mr. Reza, well, I don't see, it's hard. Right now,
I have nothing to do for yourself. Do
whatever you like. Go ahead according to the material. Because, for
example, a friend comes and reads. Now, we
don't hear anything called the word "emplom" during this period.
I say, we order
a decision. We order a pause. We have an inglof. FOP. We also have a
compression. These are the basics of our work. In the
indicators, there is also a session.
That is, if you want to
add your words, see how many times you
have watched the video so far. I have seen the entire period.
I think the period in ours is a full session.  Wait, Edonsaro,
yes, Mr. Mirzaei, are you here? Yes, Mr. Reza,
good. Mr. Mirzaei, how many times have you seen the
course? Mr. Reza, 3
times, 3 times, that is, you looked at it. Is it true?
Yes, what I told you, leave these
words aside. Was it true or not?
Because you are mostly working with words, but
in the end, you realize that they are all the same. Some of them are completely the same.
Most of them are orders. They have the same meaning. That does
n't make you come up with different words at all. You know, the
reason here is an order is that, for
example, here there was an order. Now, I
can't say, for example, "Yes, I'll teach you everything."
This is unrealistic.
Yes, because if I had all this information myself, for example, I would
tell everyone, if you had all this information, you would
be the market itself. But what that
framework shows is the market. We look at the footprints, we
study them. You learn all this
based on them. I tell yourself, you write, "
MP, you see, you see, you see, you see, you see, you see, you see, for example, "
LS, for example." Well,  That king that is the
same king that you are practicing now,
yes or a decision, yes I am also because of yes, it is all
an order, because of this I am telling you that if you
prepare your mind now, it will be easier, that is, you will
use fewer words, because later you will
look for this in another chart, well now I have come across this day, I have come across that day, I have come across a
order for the money,
we will come and check it, here in this
exercise, this is among your points, I said
send these now, I say send them,
delete these, send them again in the
format that I explained to you, yes yes,
but well, the rest, for example, in terms of drawing, now the box
and these things are very much, now of course
we sent four or five exercises, until that meeting and this meeting
we also sent two, yes Mr. Reza, I am ashamed, these past
two weeks, I have been very busy, I
work in the morning until 7 or 8,
which I generally have one or two hours of time at night,
God willing, there is no problem, now you have arrived in time,
now the holidays are over, send some, no problem,
I will shoot the whole week  Great, then a question,
Mr. Reza. We will finally get to these topics.
Now I have a child. Now I will put these
topics aside. But what
I remember from DP
in previous sessions was that the barrier had to be eaten.
Bahir would return to a place where the
decision point was DP. He would go back from the same place and give
us another Ingolf. Now,
Ingolf, did you see the previous session's problems?
No, I logged in a little bit, but I was out and not at
home. I couldn't see it completely. Oh, see
this bug fix. Definitely see the bug fix from the
previous session.
Evil's eyes. Yes, see it. My new sessions
will be uploaded next week, Thursday.
Better concepts will be explained to you and it will be smoother
.  If you don't mind, I'll watch this meeting
again now that I'm here. I'll send you the exercises.
If I
have a question at the end of the Wednesday session, I'll ask you.  It's okay if
you don't get it.  Thank you.  Please.  The next person,
number 22, is Mr. Zombi.  Hello Mr. Reza, don't be tired
.  Do you hear me?  Thank you, yes, you are
fine. Stay healthy.
This is alive, Mr. Reza. Now, ordering is
different from making a decision. We are talking about it.
The decision is
one pair. It
can be one pair. It can be no.
A decision is made in the rotations. And now I have it like this.
Now we have created a word for it. For example,
here you are in a cycle. The price is coming, it is turning, it wants to
turn, it wants to break this low. This was a
decision with its right position for this
low. The price is coming, it reacts to this, it breaks this,
then the failure does not return to this. This is the decision.
This is the swap. But, you did not return here. You go to the
lower area. You hit your bigger scale. You come back
here. It is at the order level that you should have
returned to after this failure.
Now call it whatever you want.
I am not a word.  I want you to learn
how this led to this.  Because I
wrote everything in my journal in the name of decision.  Now
that cake, well, the order with the decision, and now
I told our friend the same thing, MPL, and
something else. Finally, we say, sir, there is
an order here. Based on this procedure, for
example, there is
an order because the price has come. We draw it like
this. We say, when this is here, there was
a decision. It must have
broken these two below it. It has
turned up here. For this reason, yes, now
where did this low break? Where did this low break?
This is the order. It means that it did not return to this.
Now, whatever you call it, I do
n't want you to understand it.
For example,
say this low has broken here and it has turned
down. This is the last kink that
brought the price to that upper area
here
and this is the reverse. There was also a
reverse area here. The price has broken the low. Now,
in returning to this small area, there was another
order that was able to send the price to the lower area again.
Now, whatever you call it, let it decide.
The word for it is correct.  No,
sir, but remember it's a concept, remember it. Yes, I
had another question. The kings we decide on now
should be the closest king to the barrier.
Or can we decide now, for example, a
few kings that are taken before the level that
this level is broken
based on that 3-digit number,
based on that 3-digit number.
Now you have a broken line here
in this area.
Well, first of all, I don't think you see the bug fixes.
No, I was too busy fixing the
previous bugs and I couldn't see them. Now, from now on, I'll
force everyone to participate in fixing the bugs
because like this, when Bush comes,
our friends send the bug fixes. Only those who
participated see the bug. The
rest of the friends are rude and
don't look.
Now, for example, we have a
broken line here. Well, this king is the closest to the kink.
It broke. On the way back here, the scape was
formed. The price jumped. Now, the next line is here.
Well, this super line is useful here.
If
there is a kink in us, for example, here,
and this.  Break this box that we gave in front of a
king, that is, there should be
a king here on this area and it
itself should not return to this door. This will be
in the heart of that one
because a return here will be the last king. I will
pull it a little bit here. This will be the last king
for this line. But well, it should return to the
edge of this box. We got my box from the left
in the journal in the Saturday Refshakal. I explained this twice or three times.
Number 21, Mr. Mahdavi. Hello,
Mr. Shab
Ehsan. I think. Hello, Mr. Mahdavi. I
want you to be healthy. I think it's the same thing.
Yes, Mr. Abbasi. Mr. Abbasianeh. Yes, he changed his name again. That's
right. Don't close this
page. No, I didn't close it. At their service. At my service. Don't be
tired. I would like to invite you to be here. I am here now. Of
course, I
have a few questions. But right now, this is me. I
saw the Refshakal meeting on Saturday in Rome and it was
wonderful. Now I have to see it again
because there were important points in it. Although you will tell me later, I will tell you.
But right now, you are
here for
a moment. If you allow me.  Let me turn on my annotation, let me say, let me say, let me
be here, you said that this Lu
actually means that we will come here later to do our
investigation about this issue, we
said we are coming left, then now
you said that this Lu that is actually
broken here, you took the DP here,
then I want to know is this soup
or because because it held this, you
took this because it held this,
you took this, swap this kink,
well if swap this kink, well right here on the left,
why why is this DP, why isn't this, for example, this, why is this DP,
let me draw this,
erase your mistake
[music]
This is now swap, yes, this swap
that was created after the break of this board,
right, yes,
but, well, this big one, the way to sit, another soup,
this,
yes, just with this, well, what is the soup, that sep is one
higher, I am now compared to Lum, yes, well, what is Lu
on this Lu on what is broken, this kink means the
last one, well done, here is the last one, soup,
right, right, yes, right, then, well  The price has gone
from the top, now it has returned to this sitting position, now
this is the order consumed, now
where is the work here? Right, this is the
kink that is sitting here and everything is falling.
The kink that comes eats the lip of this breaks this,
that is, when it breaks
this area, right, let me change
this. When this king breaks, it
forms on this area.
This decision of the
price if it continues
to return to it sometimes comes back, for example, it
returns in the moment of the example here, this
king that went up, held it,
then came
eaten, its edge became like this, went down,
broke it. Yes, here it has come back, touched it and has come to a leak again.
Here, the price has a temporary reaction
to it, it hits this, then it comes down.
Basically, it itself must return to consume the order here.
If it does not consume it, it will be a
victim. In the middle of this path,
yes, you are almost done. Now, we
want to let the discussions
about this, I think about this, I should discuss it further. I am
more now because now here, now this king is the same. Yes, yes, yes,
this is completely correct
because here I am again with the edge.
Just because we actually want to see
that, for example, suppose we have 3 to 4 kings, we want to
see, for example, which of these
3 to 4 kings and suppose in the live market for
us, for example, something is the criterion
we have, you say that we should go to the
left, then because you are on the left, we can actually have
several spies, including now, maybe of
course, I'm talking a little bit, I don't know,
maybe I don't understand, for example, we also
have this one sitting on this, for
example, this big one is the spies,
but this little one is the spies, now
you here, we you took the last one, like, for
example, I ask, why don't we take it right here, the
last one, well,
this is the ratio of the spies, you can take it or the ratio of the
spies to the spies, or the left to the left, connect them,
and when this big one comes to consume this order, it does
n't matter whether it now goes under this spies
or goes under this spies, that kink that
breaks these, that kink that breaks this set, that
kink that breaks this set  It can
also be used for Lu
if he himself did not return at the time of the failure. It can be
used after Lu comes. Like here, right here, I
said in the game, he did not return.
Now, he returned here. Right there, that's
great. Then, I'm very grateful. I'll go
to my journal. How many times have you been here? Up until item
number 21, 21, I was able to figure
something out. But this is a bit clear. In
fact, you said that this actually
held and leaked one. Then, well, here,
I'll tell you something right here. Of course,
this was the reverse picture. I wasn't paying attention, but it doesn't matter.
Look, here, according to the
previous view that was in the first and
second periods, my view was that this was a
limit flag.
Then, well, this came. In fact, it rejected it. It broke
here.
And in this failure, it should actually return to
that. In fact, the supply of demand that we have here.
Then, I really, really, really,
without any particular vision, for example, I assumed that there was an
ignore here and this would definitely
return to that ignore
inside this kink flag limit.
Now, one of the  My main problem, Mr. Reza, is
that now
this is the limit flag, this is on the left, it was
like this, Mr. Reza, look, one was
actually a low like this,
then another was a low and this is like this,
now this is actually the second one, this is
now the limit flag, Mr. Reza, this is the second one,
now I know that we don't have anything to do with limit flags at all in this period,
but what does
this mean is that you have turned blue?
Look, this is now this line, if it has come,
this second one, this second one, now it is a limit flag,
not a red limit flag, my
flag is the
same red limit flag, that the mangshan is below
the way here,
right? Yes, yes, right, now it has moved a little bit,
right, this is very good, so
these soups that I drew, little by little, are
not needed at all, right,
here is a broken beat
and let's first have a broken beat here, well, the
price came in here, now in the
lower timeframe, there may have been an origin here, where
a broken beat was broken in this base and the price
returned to the broken area and  It continued,
right, I didn't understand, for example, at that time, this was
from these, now maybe I said like this, for example, I
said, in fact, there was another
thing here, another Levi here, I said,
this was actually the DP that
broke this low, the last DP that broke this low was this,
then this was the soup,
this was the swap, this was the swap, and this
little one, which will now be seen here in the
lower timeframe, for example, this is the soup,
maybe it reacted to this, I
saw it like this, it was hard, yes, you want to fall
there, in the lower timeframe, it's okay, but
for the upper timeframe, it can be seen that a
leak broke a lower area, turned around, and
the price came from above and sat down and continued on its
path, right,
very good, the second one, please, I because
the second one
has a bit of a case, I think it was much more distant, my work in the
second one, please tell me, I'm here here,
more from one direction, just more. Now I'm saying
that you understand that we should leave the same
previous view aside, in fact,
this is actually this, in the higher timeframe, this
big pause that has gone, in fact,  Well, it used to be like this
because it came and
passed, I expected that after crossing
this, it would return to the area right here and if you
remember, at that time when I had some
videos, of course, you and Keiwan, for example, actually
something here
that expanded like this
[music], I would have taken
this from behind, then, for
example, it would have been eaten
and spilled where it came from, then because I saw this, in fact,
now this has returned,
in fact, I felt
this big that I drew, the
DP broke both of these, that is, both these and
these, now here, only you,
please, affect me with this, now,
my point is right, this is blue, the
DP broke these two,
let me erase these first, your line, I understand
your question,
I am the one who held the price down,
right,
and a leaked swap that was formed before its own
decision.
Can you kill me later?  I didn't understand the soup that came
before them, this blue box that I
drew for you, right? Okay, right. Yes, it's the result of the
black breakout. Exactly.
Yes, I drew the kink swap flag limit for you here.
As a decision, I said, this is the
breakout decision. You drew this big one.
As a decision, I said, no, this blue kink is the
decision. Here, you have to fix this.
Right. Decision. Then here, yes, here, relative to the
low. Yes, you made this again. Yes,
if you look, we have a kink here.
Here,
[music], we
have a kink that the price has broken below, then it has come back and
hit the top again.
That means a breach at the bottom,
which is right. Then it came. Yes, it came in the
lower area. Now, whatever this low
breaks, this low here, this is the decision. And meta-
inorm is the decision. I said this in the troubleshooting session.
This is like, yes, then this relative
to this low is also here. Decision. If you look,
these are sitting together. Oh, this is
not coming from behind here anymore. Come on, these are
exactly right. Yes, this was very strange. My reason is
this.  I wanted to say that I wanted to justify the
price where it
came back, I wanted to justify it here, and something extraneous
and extravagant, these things that you are saying now,
later with those colors and arrows, because people get a little
lost, it will be fixed, for example, I
will give the full explanation, yes,
thank you very much, Mr. Reza, thank you, I took too much time,
please forgive me, next person
[music]
[applause]
Number 20 Mr. Abbasian,
hello, Mr. Reza, don't be tired,
hello, Mr. Abbas, Mr. Reza,
I have a question, we say that some lows are the result of a
failure, some lows are the result of a reaction, if you can
show this on the chart, I do
n't understand what you mean at all.
Now look at this low that is here,
this low that is here,
yes, that is right,
yes, this is the result of a reaction to this area,
this area that was obtained based on this lift.
Now let's look at this low,
well, this low is based on penetrating this area to
reach the target in front of it, if you
draw this low, the
kink that was before this  This means that
the kink that broke before this low broke this low, the low
broke, which itself broke,
but in the future, if this low is drawn,
it will be the result of a reaction,
as if it were not a violation, but it hits under an area.
Go up,
notice this second kink, John, the
second kink is the result of the reaction of this left. This
kink is the result of the violation
here. This is the decision.
Now in the future, that is, in the chart, when
this low breaks, the previous kink says that the kink is on the
violation,
meaning this low is the result of a reaction, which was not the result of an
ingolfing of the area.
In essence, in the low time, it goes back to the same place,
but in the high time, this golfer
does not come to
consume or eat that thing left. In its origin,
these lows
create a perspective. Now, what did this low do for this
kink? Inversely,
when you are on the right side of the kink that
breaks this low, you say that this low is the result of an
ingolfing, which was not the result of a reaction, right?
Yes,
now let's move on to the next kink, this next loop.
If a kink breaks this loop, this loop
itself is the result of a reaction. I'm
telling you, it's a violation
that it didn't have.
In fact, this loop is not very useful here. The
ones that are useful
are different from those that violate or
go and f-f somewhere. These are the ones
that violate or f-f are more important to us on the
chart. So-called
colored loops. We call these colored loops
a series of loops that are
on our chart based on that loop. Do you put a
green drop under it? Do you put a green drop under this
loop?
No, what is this loop that is the result of
this reaction? What is this loop
that has violated? For violation, is a kink that
breaks these different?
Why don't you just talk to me and
now
you have a loop here
?
What made this iron?
This kink has made nothing,
this low has made this kink again.
Oh, yes,
this has caused this to break, it will break below it. In the
return, this swap method is correct.
Now
the price is coming from above
here. One here makes a base. This
breaks. This itself returns to here. It goes
down. I drew it very badly.
One kink comes here. Here, it goes like this.
Then it goes like this. Then it goes down. It breaks.
Now, I want to draw it
against this low. You tell me.
This decision is
this decision.
Here, it is decided
which one. If you have three kings, the
last one you drew is big
because its
time frame is higher. It was decided there. Remember to
hit it
because this. Look, this is the
last kink compared to this.
But basically, there is a gap
between these. This should
return the price to this. And we can
say, sir, this was a
kink that this low was hit when it hit this low.  It
opens up, but it takes precedence
.  First it goes down, then it goes
up.  We can do this,
That means, go hit his back,
open it, then hit the lower area, do F,
and go up.   Did
you understand, Mr. Abbasi?  Finally, I didn't understand what you
said, you explained the same diagram.
Look, now that box can be the next decision.
Step by step, that box can be the decision. Where to put this?
I'll find this time. I'll
decide to break the black box.
When it breaks the black box, the price doesn't go back
inside. This was one situation. But we also have a
situation where, for example, it goes back up. If it goes back up,
it should keep the price in front of the
price. If it doesn't go back,
we should always consider that king above for this
graph. The upward violation when
the price breaks the low. It goes back and hits the back of the high box.
So you expect it to first determine the
low, then go back and hit the high box. That's
right, it's a low. But
this low is a
low because the low hasn't reached the target. Okay,
you
understand. Now, what's
the difference between a reaction low and a colored low? You understand. I
had another question. This discussion was about a high.
Sometimes it hits a king. Walk
[music]
a king. Well, then it hits a
small one. We call it a hold.  It's getting bigger, it's
penetrating into the king,
we say it's a hold. This hold is I can't
tell which king held which
king didn't.
Now look at the area here.
This king held. Why did the price come
inside the area? It hit the edge. This
edge hit. It doesn't count as a hold. It definitely has to
come inside the king and consume the king order.
Now this is a hold. So
where is the order here?
This is relative to this cake that exists here.
So relative to this king that
hit the higher price hit the edge. So this
can be
a king hold. Again,
this king
held the order. Where is the order
here? Now this is relative to now. The action he
took above and
hit an internal inflow here. He
played a market maker. He
hit it once again. This remains below this. But now this order is
inside this. The price has come to hold it. Now
again,
here you have some things that are not correct. He came
inside and held it,
meaning he came to take the order inside this.
You should see inside this
order.  Where is it,
you remember, if it hits the edge, say this is a hold,
I don't accept it, for example, if this
kink that you have here has reached this price, it has reached this, it can
be a hold, but
if it hits, I saw in your exercises that you were holding the
edges, I
said that these are not holds, the hold should come into the
order, take this king, go away,
in the future, now this area, when it
hits again under this, this will be
identified as a violation, an engraft will be identified,
okay, in your hands, the next person, number 18, easy,
I am sir, aha, now, call me sir, sir, sir,
Reza, I am getting more confused
in a number of areas, now in my journal, I think it should be
clear in the exercises that I sent,
one was in the elsa, which was resolved last night,
thanks to you,
one was pulled in this SNR, yes, yes, please
listen, yes, let me
explain this to you, I am mostly taking these in the low time,
see, sir, Ehsan, here, you look at this,
for example, now from this one, a straight line, an s
NR Back
Well
[Music] What is
the criterion for this? What is the criterion for this? What is this? It's
him. The
line
below here is a SNR. I drew it. Well, this is a snare.
Well, sir, this is a DP soup. That's right, but
this is a king. Here we have a king. A king who
broke this Lu. This Lu is broken.
Now, I don't know why you don't say
SNR. You give this Lu. Kinko. You take SNR. Now,
here is
the decision to break this Lu. This is the swap.
This DP is for breaking. It means it came from above. It
decided to say Lu broke this Lu. You take
SNR. I say, why do
n't you use these Lus? This Lu went behind this one.
Why don't you use it? I
just look at it. It led to breaking.
This was the last King that you went to beat.
I took Lu.
This Ginge went to beat. Well, Kinko himself.
I don't understand. This Lu is his own. This King.
Why do you write SNR? Write this.
Kinko who broke his last Hi. It's not like this at all. It's just
one higher.
But  Draw a box like this, now
draw a box for A, here is a Lone Lue, he has held it,
here you
draw a box for this, you write
SNR, I don't understand, I don't understand, oh,
any Lui Hai that doesn't work now, for example, this Hi
and this Lu, this Lu caused it to
break, so in the future it can
create a kink for us here, for example, or
this Lu that led to these, here again
can create a King for us, what do I know
based on this, now come on,
you, let me see now, let me get another one,
delete this from the tab,
otherwise you went and got this Lu, SNR, what is this Lu,
this Lu, SNR, what is that, where do you get it, for
example, you get this Lu,
SNR, I don't understand, what is this, how do
you get it, now we have a King here, the
Lui that led to Hier Hai or the Lui that
led to Lu, you draw from that SNR,
now this
thing  You sent
this story here, this is the story of the gold
here, the gold in this area,
so don't we have a Lu here, a Lu that
broke a high and created a higher high? Why is
n't this an SNR and this is not a kink?
You went in one second,
in 5 minutes, you drew a Lu here, you
say SR. Yes, because I'm using the low time,
by the way, I
got this kink, but for the high time, it's good.
Well, the ones you draw, it's better to
draw the kink, King, draw a kink that
has a DP swap, Lu broke the kink, but
draw it like this. Now, most of the problems
you have are based on this.
Come on, let's go. Here, you
drew a DP here.
Look here. You drew a kink SNR here.
For example, you zoomed out. The whole exercise in
one piece. Put this piece in a chart. This
piece above in a chart. That is,
separate the charts. For example, now you yourself here, God,
put yourself in my place.  Hey, now from here,
my eyes are clear that it's wrong because the ones where this Lue is
broken, this Lue is also kinked here, this
DP was broken, this kink was blue, do you
agree? Which one is more spectacular or the big box? The big box is
this VP, the
front ones are broken, the pink one is in front, that
box is Arosh Ares King, you got it,
Ares King with Ares King, you know, these are minors
in the heart of this king with this size,
how can this be?
For example, what are you doing here?  Assuming this, is
this kink true?
Then you came from this Kinke,
you drew a line on these Hayes, you say this is
Ars Kinke,
so why don't you say this Kinke that the last Hay
broke here, on the contrary, DP that this Hay
broke, draw Ars
from these big lows and important times,
those who go higher, make a higher high and
a new low,
or make an
Ace, they cause a failure, or the last low, the
Hayes in your rotations, based on them,
take these, yes, in the meeting of that Flash
Rangia, I
understand another issue that I had, for
example, what time can you bring the gold now,
Mr. Reza, here we
had something, we had a DP failure,
then on this Hay that had a comeback, an
R came on top, made the price up,
now it has come under it, right,
draw a line so that I can draw a line later, yes,
see, we had a Hay here, well, this
came, gave us an Ars King,
this is the bottom, the DP was broken, then
this R that was formed here was criticized
here  We had some, now why did we say 4
hours ago, it was clear that the
grips here were here,
this one came, violated it,
violated the arc, then yes, we came and well,
Kane, who had not violated the sub,
no, we did not hit this sub, but well, I will follow these in a way
to
reach the lower areas, and now he has
come here, he has formed this, this will be the
soup of the arc,
this is not confirmed now, we want to swap it,
but Lu has passed the lu, you want to move the king around it, no, it is not
confirmed yet,
so what box will you draw, so this is, in times like this, so
I have to wait and see what happens with
this first, will it hit the hay or will it hit the lu,
then I will decide on it, yes, I mean, here right now, there is
no house, and there is nothing,
see, we make our trades based on the decisions of the
pawns.
Well, this is about this, but now you have a problem with the
basics. Now, there's nothing left to trade. Did
n't I tell you why this
happened? Don't you know that this should
come? The mouse is broken. Do
n't you know that this should come here, hit it under this line,
hit it here
to be confirmed? How are you pulling
the box here? You came with this, it went higher, you move the
box, you take it up with it.
Yes, that was exactly my question because
up here, in one of the photos I sent you,
this is in this area,
I looked here in the lower time frame,
a DP like this has formed
here that this hasn't reached.
You trade with these, ISA,
places like this, you trade now,
yes, you trade now,
but it gets confusing like this.
Why are you trading now? I'm
practicing now. I mean, you trade with a relay or a
demo account, I
mean, you
practice with a prop account.
Well, now that
the price is coming down from here, what did this
low
and this high do?  One before and one
before, it
means that the higher the higher the lower the lower. Well, we
have two important areas here because the higher the higher the higher the higher the lower
Something is coming here, an
area is coming here, relative to this low, this door,
this crack, this kink, this pain, the
cord, here, now this price has come from above and
below, you have looted here, here is
a low that is here, with this range,
our king, to give it to him, there has been a series of reactions,
that is, here is the lip, that is the area below me, that is,
this lip, this is the
area below me, that is, in the return, this is the
cake, the upper area, right? Yes,
well, we got this based on the low left. Here, well,
from now on, we got our low based on this king, we can
see the top
here,
this kink,
well, what's wrong with this? Now, you
tell me, what's wrong with this?
I was here on this layer, this is the DP,
for the failures of this, I draw a line, this is the DP,
so this is the same swap, it will be, again, yes,
then here, this swap, I got it,
then I got this swap, it seemed to me
that the price should come into this area, like this,
behind this,
yes, behind this, you are more
effortless.  Don't do it if you want to at least let your
theory sessions finish. Then,
after your theory sessions are over,
decide whether you want to do the exercise on a
demo account because you wo
n't get any results if you get a prop account. If you do this, you
should learn better topics than what you
think.
Now, maybe I don't know anything. Now, what should I say?
You should know at least four of the teaching sessions.
These are the things you have to do. Compare them with the
materials you have.
See if
your mindset is right.
Some
basic rules. You saw this golf. If you want to
trade in the retracement, you should know your orders or decisions. That is, you want to do it like this.
Before it is
confirmed, then wherever we don't take
this golf, we have to see where the price comes from. First,
from the target, from the area. I mean, I'll show you an
example now. Now, it's time for the
next person to read the rest. You
look here. You see, the price started from this low and
went up 10 places, which is under the table. That is,
wherever you say, it comes under the table here.
Put the price here, it's under here,
put the line, it's under here,
put the price here, put the line, it's under here, put the price here, it's under here, put the price here, it's under here,
put the price here, it's under here, well, all of this, all of you
Hello, my
dear friends and colleagues. I am very happy to be with
you with the new Zeus Group Trading Course.  This course is published in its entirety
in a dedicated playlist of the same name on
Zeus' official YouTube page at Zeus Forex
Channel, and all sessions can be viewed in order from the
first episode.  In this course,
you will see 9 one-hour teaching sessions
presented conceptually and practically.  After
watching each session, you can practice
and then watch 6 short half-hour sessions of
troubleshooting by friends who participated in the round
to get a better understanding of the material.
After that, enter the next teaching session.
To communicate directly with us and use the
troubleshooting plans, simply send a message to the Telegram ID of
Zeus Group Underline of this admin and
stay in touch with us.  Wishing you all success
in your trading career, my
dears.
[Music]